PROFILE

Full-stack developer with front-end tendencies who has five years industry experience in mobile/web application development, cloud computing, software architecture and automated testing/deployment. Proficient in programming languages and current web technologies (NodeJS, HTML/CSS, C/C++, Java, PHP, MySQL, Git).

EDUCATION

University Of Nevada Las Vegas, las Vegas, nv

(in progress)

Post-Baccalaureate Certificate in Health Career Professional Studies

UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA RENO, Reno, NV

December 2013

Master's in Business Administration – GPA: 3.88

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA LOS ANGELES, Los Angeles, CA

June 2010

Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science – GPA: 2.89

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INTERNATIONAL GAME TECHNOLOGY, Reno, NV

June 2010 - May 2014

Systems R&D – Software Engineer II

- iOS developer on a Dutch-style auction based mobile app which uses casino loyalty comps as currency.
- Knowledgeable in client-server technologies such as REST API calls and JSON/XML parsing.
- Led effort in using continuous integration testing tools and deployment tools Jenkins and Testflight.
- Integrated functional testing tools such as MonkeyTalk for automated testing of builds.
- Experience in project methodologies such as the waterfall model, agile scrum, and pair programming.

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Research

Fall 2016

- Assist in weekly field day of harvest and collecting data on desert plant species in the Sheep Mountain Range
- Participated in weekly journal club with research group to discuss scientific publications.

Undergraduate Teacher Assistant

Principles of Modern Biology II Lab

Fall 2016

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Volunteering

The Animal Foundation, Las Vegas, NV

June 2016 – Current

- Canine companion that provides socialization and enrichment to dogs available for adoption
- Assisted in events: Clear The Shelter Day, New Volunteer Orientation, Dog Costume Contest

Asian American Tutorial Project, Los Angeles, CA

Fall 2006 – Fall 2009

Tutor and socialize with underprivileged children at Castelar Street Elementary in Chinatown every Saturday morning during the Fall, Winter, and Spring semesters

GAP YEARS May 2014 – May 2016

- Gained a fresh perspective on the world after traveling through 29 countries over the span of a year including an extended solo backpacking adventure for four months throughout Europe and Asia
- Adapted to many different cultures and languages while sharpening my negotiation and interpersonal skills
- Developed better understanding of construction, planning, and budgeting working with father on two renovation projects that overhauled a 3000 square feet commercial unit and 5000 square feet residential building